songs420.com 2008-08-20

# Ansarimusic The World Of Music On It's Peak

The Way Musicbenz.com Uses Information 

1\. If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Musicbenz.com Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Musicbenz.com Sites. 

2\. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the Musicbenz.com Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the Musicbenz.com Sites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

3\. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Musicbenz.com Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

4\. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Musicbenz.com Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

5\. We use cookies, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Musicbenz.com Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

When Musicbenz.com discloses Information 

Musicbenz.com reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that Musicbenz.com believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Musicbenz.com, our Users or others. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice 

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the Musicbenz.com Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

\-------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

The use of this version of the Musicbenz.com website(s) and/or Musicbenz.com software and any other related software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers (the "Service") provided by Musicbenz.com inc. ("Musicbenz.com") are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

General Musicbenz.com takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information, which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. 

BY USING OR ACCESSING ANY Musicbenz.com WEBSITE OR DOWNLOADING AND USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. Musicbenz.com MAY AMEND THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME. 

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Service, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. 

Collection of Information 

Personal Information: Use of certain features of the Service may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nick name (or other user ID) and a password. 

Non personally identifiable Information: Musicbenz.com may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Musicbenz.com Service or website(s), and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on Musicbenz.com''s Service and/or website(s). 

Musicbenz.com may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non personally identifiable technical information, when the Musicbenz.com website(s) and pages are visited or when the Musicbenz.com Service is used. 

How is the information being used? 

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by Musicbenz.com, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you ; to fulfill your requests for Services, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Service and/or website(s), offerings and advertisements presented on Musicbenz.com Service, email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other Services, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

Any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. Musicbenz.com may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of Musicbenz.com users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures. 

Cookies 

Musicbenz.com may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Service and/or of Musicbenz.com''s web sites, including to operate and improve offerings through the Service and/or web sites; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Service, and/or web sites; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you. 

Additionally, Musicbenz.com or its advertisers may use other companies known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Service, and/or web sites. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements'' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not Musicbenz.com''s. 

Musicbenz.com does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Services and/or web sites may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. 

Special Note for Parents 

Musicbenz.com''s Service and websites are intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen (13) are not permitted to register with Musicbenz.com''s Service and websites. 

Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information 

Deletion (Opt-Out). In order to delete the personally identifiable information you submitted, notify us, to the following email address: support(-at-)Musicbenz.com.com that you wish to delete your personally identifiable information or any part thereof contained at our databases. 

Modification. If you wish to modify or update your personally identifiable information, use the web-site or application interface. If you need help, please contact us at the following email address: support(-at-)Musicbenz.com.com 

Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from Musicbenz.com''s database will not prevent Musicbenz.com from using gathered anonymous information. 

Third Parties'' Practices. 

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other provides of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that Musicbenz.com does not own or control, or does not employ or manage.
